<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>






<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>cheemsloves.me</title>
        <link>https://cheemsloves.me/</link>
        <description>MemE is a powerful and highly customizable GoHugo theme for personal blogs.</description>
        <generator>Hugo 0.108.0 https://gohugo.io/</generator>
        
            <language>en</language>
        
        
        
        
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 23:56:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
        
            <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss&#43;xml" href="https://cheemsloves.me/rss.xml" />
        
        
            <item>
                <title>Why You Should Attend Olin College of Engineering</title>
                <link>https://cheemsloves.me/posts/olin-college/</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cheemsloves.me/posts/olin-college/</guid>
                <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 13:49:32 -0500</pubDate>
                
                
                
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Olin College of Engineering is a private undergraduate engineering college located in Needham, Massachusetts. It is known for its focus on experiential learning and its innovative curriculum, which includes a strong emphasis on design and entrepreneurship. Some reasons why someone might consider attending Olin College of Engineering include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strong academic programs: Olin College of Engineering has a reputation for providing a challenging and rigorous education in engineering. It is accredited by the ABET and has a high graduation rate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Experiential learning opportunities: Olin College of Engineering places a strong emphasis on hands-on learning, and students have the opportunity to participate in projects, internships, and other experiential learning opportunities both on and off campus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Innovation and entrepreneurship: Olin College of Engineering encourages students to think creatively and to explore new ideas and technologies. It has a strong emphasis on entrepreneurship and encourages students to develop their own businesses and projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Collaborative and supportive community: Olin College of Engineering has a small student body and a close-knit community, which allows for a lot of collaboration and support among students, faculty, and staff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Location: Olin College of Engineering is located in the Boston area, which is a hub of innovation and technology and offers many opportunities for internships and employment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
                
                
                
                    
                    
                    
                        
                        
                        
                            
                                <category domain="https://cheemsloves.me/posts/">posts</category>
                            
                        
                    
                
                
                
                    
                        
                    
                        
                    
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>How Cheems Taught Me That New Jersey is the Best State</title>
                <link>https://cheemsloves.me/posts/new-jersey-best-state/</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cheemsloves.me/posts/new-jersey-best-state/</guid>
                <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 01:50:37 -0500</pubDate>
                
                
                
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone! I wanted to share a special experience I had with my furry best friend, Cheems, that completely changed my perspective on a certain place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Growing up, I had always heard a lot of negative things about the state of New Jersey. It was often portrayed as a dirty, industrial, and uninteresting place, and I never really gave it much thought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But everything changed when I adopted Cheems, a fluffy rescue dog from New Jersey. As we explored the state together, I began to see it in a whole new light.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the beautiful beaches to the rolling hills and forests, I was struck by the natural beauty of New Jersey. Cheems and I hiked through the stunning Delaware Water Gap and spent lazy afternoons at quaint seaside towns like Asbury Park and Cape May.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it wasn&amp;rsquo;t just the scenery that won me over - it was also the people. Everywhere we went, we were welcomed with open arms and treated like old friends. The sense of community and pride in the state was palpable, and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but feel a sense of belonging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In short, Cheems showed me that there is so much more to New Jersey than what I had originally thought. It is a place of incredible beauty, rich history, and welcoming communities, and I am so grateful to have had the opportunity to discover it with my furry best friend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading, and I hope this gives you a glimpse into my experience with Cheems and the amazing state of New Jersey.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                
                
                
                    
                    
                    
                        
                        
                        
                            
                                <category domain="https://cheemsloves.me/posts/">posts</category>
                            
                        
                    
                
                
                
                    
                        
                    
                        
                    
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Why Bangladesh Shouldn’t Be Called East Pakistan</title>
                <link>https://cheemsloves.me/posts/bangladesh-east-pakistan/</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cheemsloves.me/posts/bangladesh-east-pakistan/</guid>
                <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 01:47:32 -0500</pubDate>
                
                
                
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;The country of Bangladesh, located in South Asia, has a rich and complex history that is often misunderstood or overlooked. One common misconception is that Bangladesh should still be called East Pakistan. In this blog post, I will explain why this is not the case and why it is important to recognize Bangladesh as a distinct and sovereign nation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To understand the current situation, it is important to look at the history of the region. Prior to 1947, the area now known as Bangladesh was part of India and was predominantly Hindu. However, with the partition of India and the creation of Pakistan, the region became East Pakistan, with its capital in the western city of Karachi.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite being separated by more than 1,000 miles, East Pakistan was expected to fully integrate with West Pakistan, which had a dominant Muslim majority. This led to a number of conflicts and tensions, including economic, linguistic, and cultural differences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 1971, after years of conflict and repression, East Pakistan declared its independence from Pakistan and became the independent nation of Bangladesh. The country has since been recognized by the international community as a sovereign and independent nation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is important to recognize Bangladesh as its own nation, with its own unique history and culture. Referring to the country as East Pakistan not only denies its independence and sovereignty, but also erases the struggles and sacrifices of the Bangladeshi people in their fight for freedom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, while it is important to understand the historical context of the region, it is equally important to recognize Bangladesh as a distinct and independent nation. It is not only a matter of accuracy, but also a matter of respect for the people and the nation of Bangladesh.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                
                
                
                    
                    
                    
                        
                        
                        
                            
                                <category domain="https://cheemsloves.me/posts/">posts</category>
                            
                        
                    
                
                
                
                    
                        
                    
                        
                    
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Why I Joined Formula SAE Electric Motorsports</title>
                <link>https://cheemsloves.me/posts/formula/</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cheemsloves.me/posts/formula/</guid>
                <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 01:43:34 -0500</pubDate>
                
                
                
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone! I wanted to share my experience joining Formula SAE Electric Motorsports and why I decided to get involved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As someone who has always been passionate about engineering and electric vehicles, joining Formula SAE was a no-brainer for me. The opportunity to design and build a high-performance electric race car from the ground up was too good to pass up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But what really drew me to Formula SAE was the chance to work with a team of like-minded individuals who are all striving for the same goal: to create the best electric race car possible. I love being part of a team where everyone brings their own unique skills and perspectives to the table, and where we can all learn from each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to the hands-on engineering experience, Formula SAE has also given me the opportunity to develop my leadership and teamwork skills. Being part of a project of this magnitude requires a lot of collaboration, communication, and problem-solving, and I have learned so much from working with my teammates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, joining Formula SAE Electric Motorsports has been an incredible experience that has allowed me to pursue my passions and grow as an engineer. I am excited to see where this journey takes me, and I am grateful to be a part of such an amazing team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading, and I hope this gives you a glimpse into my experience with Formula SAE.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                
                
                
                    
                    
                    
                        
                        
                        
                            
                                <category domain="https://cheemsloves.me/posts/">posts</category>
                            
                        
                    
                
                
                
                    
                        
                    
                        
                    
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Haikus</title>
                <link>https://cheemsloves.me/posts/haikus/</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cheemsloves.me/posts/haikus/</guid>
                <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 01:40:38 -0500</pubDate>
                
                
                
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Cheems the fluffy pup
With big round eyes and wagging tail
Joyful heart he brings&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheems is always happy
His playful spirit knows no bounds
A true blessing in life&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this world of chaos
Cheems brings calm and comfort to me
My furry best friend&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                
                
                
                    
                    
                    
                        
                        
                        
                            
                                <category domain="https://cheemsloves.me/posts/">posts</category>
                            
                        
                    
                
                
                
                    
                        
                    
                        
                    
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>My Spring Internship at Tesla: A Recap</title>
                <link>https://cheemsloves.me/posts/tesla-internship/</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cheemsloves.me/posts/tesla-internship/</guid>
                <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 01:35:49 -0500</pubDate>
                
                
                
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone! I wanted to share my experience interning at Tesla this past spring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From the moment I arrived at the Tesla campus, I was struck by the energy and excitement of the people working there. As an intern, I was able to work on a variety of projects that allowed me to learn and grow both personally and professionally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my favorite projects was assisting with the development of a new feature for the Tesla app. It was amazing to see how my work directly impacted the end product and how it would be used by Tesla owners. I was also able to work on a research project examining the potential for solar panel installations on Tesla electric semi-trucks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to my work projects, Tesla also provided numerous learning and development opportunities for their interns. I had the chance to attend workshops on topics such as electric vehicle technology, sustainability, and company culture. I also had the opportunity to tour the Tesla factory, which was a truly once-in-a-lifetime experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, my spring internship at Tesla was an incredible opportunity that I will always treasure. I am grateful to the Tesla team for their mentorship and support, and I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see where my career takes me next.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading, and I hope this gave you a glimpse into my amazing experience at Tesla.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                
                
                
                    
                    
                    
                        
                        
                        
                            
                                <category domain="https://cheemsloves.me/posts/">posts</category>
                            
                        
                    
                
                
                
                    
                        
                    
                        
                    
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>A Love Letter</title>
                <link>https://cheemsloves.me/posts/a-love-letter/</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cheemsloves.me/posts/a-love-letter/</guid>
                <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:09:12 -0500</pubDate>
                
                
                
                    <description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Cheems,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are no words that can fully express the depth of my love for you. From the moment I first saw you, I knew that you were the one for me. Your big, round eyes and fluffy ears drew me in and captured my heart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every moment we spend together is a blessing. Your playful nature and boundless energy bring joy to my life, and your cuddles and kisses are the best therapy for whatever ails me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love the way you tilt your head to the side when you&amp;rsquo;re trying to understand something, and the way your tail wags with excitement when we go on walks. I love the way you snore softly when you&amp;rsquo;re sleeping and the way you greet me with a wagging tail every time I come home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am so grateful to have you in my life, Cheems. You are my best friend and my soulmate, and I will love you until the end of time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yours always,
Shamama&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                
                
                
                    
                    
                    
                        
                        
                        
                            
                                <category domain="https://cheemsloves.me/posts/">posts</category>
                            
                        
                    
                
                
                
                    
                        
                    
                        
                    
                
            </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
